Zagoria, Sam National Labor Relations Board Papers 6379
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Sam Zagoria National Labor Relations Board Papers
1940-2007
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Zagoria, Sam
6379
1.5 cubic feet
1.5 linear ft.
Papers.
8451015
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, April 18, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, September 14, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6379 MB: Sam Zagoria National Labor Relations Board Memorabilia 6379 P: Sam Zagoria, National Labor Relations Board Photographs
Johnson, Lyndon Baines, 1908-1973; Nixon, Richard Milhous, 1913-1974; Zagoria, Samuel; National Labor Relations Board (NLRB); U.S. Conference of Mayors
8451015
- News Clippings, 1944-1965 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Sam Zagoria Sworn in as Member of NLRB, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- NLRB Appointment and Swearing In, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Scope and Contents
  Dismantled scrapbook
- NLRB Career, 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Dismantled scrapbook. Photographs removed to 6379 P, box 1:ff 5
- NLRB Career, 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Dismantled scrapbook. Photographs removed to 6379 P, box 1:ff 6
- Career at U.S. Conference of Mayors, 1970-1979 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Dismantled scrapbook. Photographs removed to 6379 P, box 1:ff 4
- Articles by Sam Zagoria, 1965-1978 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Cities Collide With the Unions, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Fifth Annual Employee Relations and Management Conference, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- The Ombudsman, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Awards, 1951-1968 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Senator John Cooper Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- White House Christmas Cards (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Rutgers Interview with Sam Zagoria, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Scissors and Letter Opener, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  In a leather case. Letter opener inscribed: "Sam Zagoria NLRB 1965-1969" Removed to Collection 6379 MB.
- FBI File, 1965-1997 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Biographical Information, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Labor-Management Relations Service, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Writings By and About Sam Zagoria, 1940-2006 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Certificates, 1941-1945 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Florida Atlantic University Teaching, 1984-1991 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Organization Outline for Local Public Relations Committees, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  New Jersey Defense Council Manual no.9
- National Labor Relations Board Career [dismantled scrapbook], 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  For photographs from this scrapbook see collection 6379 P
- Commissioner, U.S. Consumer Product Safety Commission Appointment [dismantled scrapbook], 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Washington Post Clippings, 1946-1955 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Nieman Fellowship, 1954-1955 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- E-Streeters, 1976-1984 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  "E-Streeters" was the social group of Washington Post staff retirees who had worked in the ragged E Street Post building and then moved to more luxurious quarters at 1500 L Street NW.
- American Newspaper Guild, 1952-1960 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Senator Clifford Case, 1955-1965 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- National Labor Relations Board (NLRB), 1965-1970 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Labor-Management Relations Service (LMRS), 1970-1978 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Federal Election Commission Nomination, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Consumer Product Safety Commission, 1978-1983 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Washington Post Ombudsman, 1983-1987 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Fulbright (Denmark), 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Biographies and Obituaries, 1942-1959 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Biographies and Obituaries, 1942-1959 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- National Committee for a Fair Minimum Wage, 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- War Bond Division Publicity [folder 1 of 2], 1942-1945 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  Printed posters and miscellaneous
- War Bond Division Publicity [folder 2 of 2], 1942-1945 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Mimeographed posters; Music; Transcriptions; The Mail; Sales Stimulators; Unit Newspapers; Aiding the War Bond Officer; Life Insurance; "War Bond Flashes"; Miscellaneous